<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  ~ Copyright (C) 2017-2022  Dominic Joas
  ~
  ~ This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or
  ~ modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License
  ~ as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 3
  ~ of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
  -->

<resources>
    <string name="help_start">
        <![CDATA[
            <h1>Home screen</h1>
            <div class="ce-bodytext">
                <p>
                    Various widgets are displayed on the start screen, which can be selected in the settings.
                </p>
                <p>
                    Data records can be searched across modules using the magnifying glass.
                </p>
                <p>
                    The refresh button updates all visible widgets.
                </p>
                <p>
                    The menu takes you to the settings and to the export / import.
                </p>
            </div>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_export_import">
        <![CDATA[
            <h1>Export/Import</h1>
            <div class="ce-bodytext">
                <p>
                    Here it is possible to export data from the app in different formats or to import data into the app.
                </p>
                <p>
                    One can export to a PDF file, a text file, a CSV file or an XML file<br>
                    and import data from a text file, a CSV file or an XML file.
                </p>
                <p>
                    You can export or import data from all modules. It is possible to select all data sets or only certain ones.
                </p>
            </div>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_settings">
        <![CDATA[
            <h1>Settings</h1>
            <div class="ce-bodytext">
                <p>
                    You can get to the settings screen by touching "Settings" in the menu on the start screen.
                </p>
                <p>
                    Here you can choose between 4 main categories:
                </p>
                <ol>
                    <li>General (general settings)</li>
                    <li>Start screen (settings for the wigets on the start screen)</li>
                    <li>Thematic settings (settings for the modules)</li>
                    <li>Export / import (settings for the interfaces)</li>
                </ol>
            </div>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_marklist">
        <![CDATA[
            <h1>Note lists</h1>
            <div class="ce-bodytext">
                <p>
                    In this module it is possible to create point grade lists, which you need as a grade list for class work.
                </p>
                <p>
                    There are different types of lists: linear, with kinks, exponential and IHK.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>Dictation mode:</strong><br>
                    There is no number of points in dictation mode
                    which must be achieved, but a number of errors,
                    which can be achieved for a maximum of one grade.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>Linear note list:</strong><br>
                    The linear grade list is the simplest list.
                     You can specify a maximum number of points, indicate whether there are tenth or quarter grades and
                     you can set whether there are whole or half points.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>List of notes with curtsey:</strong><br>
                    Here you can also specify a number of points
                    until when there is the best or worst grade.
                    And an additional note and the associated points.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>Exponential Note-list:</strong><br>
                    Setting the same as for the linear note list.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>IHK grade list:</strong><br>
                    Setting the same as for the linear note list.
                </p>
                <p>&nbsp;</p>
                <p>
                    <strong>Menu:</strong><br>
                    In the menu you can find a list of notes with their settings
                     set as default or save grade lists.
                     You also get to the expanded graphical view here.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>Extended graphical view:</strong><br>
                    The list of grades is shown graphically here.
                     The switches can be used to adjust the settings
                     and in the menu you can export the settings.
                </p>
            </div>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_calculate_mark">
        <![CDATA[
            <h1>Calculate grades</h1>
            <div class="ce-bodytext">
                <p>
                    Here you can by giving results in class tests
                    and tests calculate the current grade point average.
                </p>
                <p>
                    By pressing the buttons in the footer area, years or subjects can be added.
                </p>
                <p>
                    If you have selected a year or a subject in the header area
                     A round button appears in the footer area.
                     If you press on it you can create a new class test or test.
                     you can weight them differently by specifying the weighting.
                </p>
            </div>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_timetable">
        <![CDATA[
            <h1>Timetable</h1>
            <div class="ce-bodytext">
                <p>
                    Here you can enter new timetables for a year.
                </p>
                <p>
                    By pressing the buttons in the foot area you can compartments,
                    Add classes, teachers, years and times.
                </p>
                <p>
                    If you give known abbreviations to the subjects of the app,
                    these are added automatically.
                </p>
                <p>
                    If you indicate the beginning of the hour at the times
                    the end is automatically switched to the beginning by 45 minutes.
                </p>
                <p>
                    If you press one of the blue boxes in the timetable entry, a dialog opens,
                    in which you can specify the subject, the teacher and a room number.
                </p>
            </div>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_notes">
        <![CDATA[
            <h1>Notes</h1>
            <div class="ce-bodytext">
                <p>
                    Here you can enter notes.
                </p>
                <p>
                    If you press the microphone, you can dictate it to the app.
                </p>
                <p>
                    If title says, the following part is entered as title,
                    if you say description, the following part is entered as description.
            </div>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_todo">
        <![CDATA[
            <h1>ToDo-Lists</h1>
            <div class="ce-bodytext">
                <p>
                    Here you can add to-do lists.
                </p>
                <p>
                    If you press the button in the footer area, you can enter new ToDo lists.
                </p>
                <p>
                    If you select a list in the header area, you can add new todos by pressing the plus.
                </p>
                <p>
                    Here you can set different priorities.
                </p>
            </div>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_timer">
        <![CDATA[
            <h1>School-Timer</h1>
            <div class="ce-bodytext">
                <p>
                    Here you can add new events.
                </p>
                <p>
                    You can search for a date in the upper part or use the arrows to change the day.
                </p>
                <p>
                    By pressing the plus you can add an event.
                </p>
            </div>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_learning_cards">
        <![CDATA[
            <h1>Learning-Cards</h1>
            <div class="ce-bodytext">
                <p>
                    Here you can create index cards and be queried.
                </p>
                <p>
                    In the foot area you can use the buttons for subjects, teachers,
                    Create groups or index cards and queries.
                </p>
            </div>
        ]]>
    </string>
</resources>